Guide to the Media Services Audio and Video Recordings, 1963 - ongoing UA.10.03.0003
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Media Services Audio and Video Recordings
1963 - ongoing
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Duke University. Auxiliary Services. Media Services
UA.10.03.0003
31 Linear Feet
Media Services (also referred to as Duke Studios) provides broadcast quality media production services to all parts of the Duke University community. Its services include video and audio production and post-production (including event documentation), project design, production equipment rentals, tape duplication, custom CDs and DVDs, and computer graphics and animation. Collection includes audio and video recordings of campus events, programming produced for various university offices and departments, and musical recordings. Campus events include basketball, football, the inaugurations of presidents Richard Brodhead, Keith Brodie, and Nannerl Keohane, dedication of the Doris Duke Memorial, the retirement and funeral of Terry Sanford, events related to September 11, 2001, a remembrance of Benjamin N. Duke, and commencement ceremonies. Authors, scholars, and other notable people represented include John Hope Franklin, Jesse Jackson, Reynolds Price, Ronald Reagan, Elie Wiesel, Billy Graham, C. D. Wright, Gerald Barrax, Elizabeth Cox, Tim McLaurin, Eric Meyers, Orrin Pilkey, and Alex Roland. Musical recordings include the Duke University Concert Band, Dan Locklair, and 1980s rock band the X-Teens.
Access Restrictions
Researchers must register and agree to copyright and privacy laws before using this collection.
All or portions of this collection may be housed off-site in Duke University's Library Service Center. The library may require up to 48 hours to retrieve these materials for research use.
Use of audiotapes and videotapes from this collection requires the creation of reference copies. Reference copies for some of the tapes have been made, and if a reference copy exists, it is noted in this finding aid. To arrange for the creation of reference copies of other items, please contact University Archives staff. Although these recordings are now stored in a stable environment, their condition and playback quality is unknown.
Provenance
The Media Services Audio and Video Recordings was received by the University Archives as transfers in 1989-2014, accession numbers UA89-0059, UA93-144, UA94-136, UA96-115, UA97-6, UA97-57, UA2003-20, UA2003-23, UA2005-14, UA2005-45, UA2009-0026, UA2009-0035, UA2011-0007, and UA2014-0018.
Historical Note
Media Services (also referred to as Duke Studios) provides broadcast quality media production services to all parts of the Duke University community. Duke Studios was established in 1980 as an audio production facility in the Biddle Building on East Campus. In 1989, it moved to the Bryan Center on West Campus. It has expanded its services to include video and audio production and post-production (including event documentation), project design, production equipment rentals, tape duplication, custom CDs and DVDs, and computer graphics and animation.
Media Services was formerly known as Technical Services and was a division of Auxiliary Services. Media Services and Technical Services later became two separate departments within Event Management, a Division of Auxiliary Services. Technical Services provides technical support services including audio-visual rentals, sound reinforcement, and audio-visual maintenance and support in many campus facilities. Technical Services assists departments and student organizations throughout the Duke campus including Duke Athletics, academic classes and meetings, student organized bands and speakers, and sound systems for University-wide events such as Graduation and Convocation.
Collection Overview
Collection includes audio and video recordings of campus events, programming produced for various university offices and departments, and musical recordings. Campus events include basketball, football, the inaugurations of presidents Richard Brodhead, Keith Brodie, and Nannerl Keohane, dedication of the Doris Duke Memorial, the retirement and funeral of Terry Sanford, events related to September 11, 2001, a remembrance of Benjamin N. Duke, and commencement ceremonies. Authors, scholars, and other notable people represented include John Hope Franklin, Jesse Jackson, Reynolds Price, Ronald Reagan, Elie Wiesel, Billy Graham, C. D. Wright, Gerald Barrax, Elizabeth Cox, Tim McLaurin, Eric Meyers, Orrin Pilkey, and Alex Roland. Musical recordings include the Duke University Concert Band, Dan Locklair, and 1980s rock band the X-Teens.
Video recordings; Sound recordings; September 11 Terrorist Attacks, 2001 -- Social aspects; Franklin, John Hope, 1915-2009; Duke University -- Football; Duke University -- Commencement ceremonies; Duke University -- Basketball; Cox, Elizabeth, 1942-; Brodie, H. Keith H. (Harlow Keith Hammond), 1939-; Barrax, Gerald W.; Keohane, Nannerl O., 1940-; Locklair, Dan; McLaurin, Tim; Duke University. Auxiliary Services. Media Services; Duke University. Auxiliary Services. Technical Services; Price, Reynolds, 1933-2011; Duke University. Concert Band; Duke University. Duke Studios; Wiesel, Elie, 1928-; Wright, C. D., 1949-; Sanford, Terry; Brodhead, Richard H., 1947-; X-Teens (Musical group); Meyers, Eric M.; Pilkey, Orrin H., 1934-; Roland, Alex, 1944-
- Video Recordings, 1980-2005, undated; 1
  - Athletics, 1985-2001, undated; 1.1
    - Athletic Complex Naming Gift Presentation, 1997 January 11; betacam-sp (Box 1, Video-cassette UA10030003-Bcam-0015)
    - Athletic Complex Naming Gift Presentation, 1997 January 11; betacam-sp (Box 1, Video-cassette UA10030003-Bcam-0016)
    - Basketball: Basketball Team Returns, 1988 April 5; 3/4-inch (Box 1, Video-cassette UA10030003-Umatic-0024)
    - Basketball: Basketball Team Returns, 1988 April 5; 3/4-inch (Box 1, Video-cassette UA10030003-Umatic-0025)
    - Basketball: Basketball Team Returns, 1989 April 4; 3/4-inch (Box 1, Video-cassette UA10030003-Umatic-0026)
    - Basketball: Duke Basketball Retrospective, circa 1985-1990; VHS (Box 1, Video-cassette UA10030003-VHS-0027)
    - Basketball: Duke vs. Cornell, 1988 December 29; 3/4-inch (Box 1, Video-cassette UA10030003-Umatic-0027)
    - Football $5 Million, undated; betacam-sp (Box 1, Video-cassette UA10030003-Bcam-0021)
    - Football: Coca-Cola Bowl, 1991 December 1; betacam-sp (Box 1, Video-cassette UA10030003-Bcam-0017)
    - Football: Coca-Cola Bowl, 1991 December 1; betacam-sp (Box 1, Video-cassette UA10030003-Bcam-0018)
    - Football: Coca-Cola Bowl, 1991 December 1; betacam-sp (Box 1, Video-cassette UA10030003-Bcam-0019)
    - Football: Coca-Cola Bowl, 1991 December 1; betacam-sp (Box 1, Video-cassette UA10030003-Bcam-0020)
    - Football: Wake Forest, 1987 January 21; 3/4-inch (Box 1, Video-cassette UA10030003-Umatic-0028)
    - Golf: 2001 NCAA Golf Championships, 2001 April 9; mini-dv (Box 1, Video-cassette UA10030003-MiniDV-0001)
  - Campus Events, 1980-2005, undated; 1.2
    - Ambitions Realized: A Nod to Nan, 2002 October 3; DVCAM (Box 3, Video-cassette UA10030003-DVCAM-0033)
      Scope and Contents
      8 minutes
    - Bill King Anniversary, undated; betacam-sp (Box 3, Video-cassette UA10030003-Bcam-0043)
    - Bill King Anniversary, undated; betacam-sp (Box 3, Video-cassette UA10030003-Bcam-0044)
    - Bill King Anniversary, undated; betacam-sp (Box 3, Video-cassette UA10030003-Bcam-0045)
    - Bryan Center Groundbreaking, circa 1980; 3/4-inch (Box 2, Video-cassette UA10030003-Umatic-0036)
    - Bryan Center Groundbreaking, circa 1980; 3/4-inch (Box 2, Video-cassette UA10030003-Umatic-0037)
    - Bryan Center Groundbreaking, circa 1980; 3/4-inch (Box 2, Video-cassette UA10030003-Umatic-0038)
    - Bryan Center Groundbreaking, circa 1980; VHS (Box 2, Video-cassette UA10030003-VHS-0030)
    - Campaign for Duke Press Conference, 1998 October 1; betacam-sp (Box 2, Video-cassette UA10030003-Bcam-0028)
    - Campaign for Duke Press Conference, 1998 October 1; betacam-sp (Box 2, Video-cassette UA10030003-Bcam-0029)
    - Chapel Choir China Tour, 1997; VHS (Box 2, Video-cassette UA10030003-VHS-0031)
    - Christmas in Duke Chapel, 1998; betacam-sp (Box 3, Video-cassette UA10030003-Bcam-0029)
    - Chuck Peseski: Mech. Eng. Experiment, Tape 2, circa 1980-1990; 3/4-inch (Box 5, Video-cassette UA10030003-Umatic-0041)
    - Doris Duke Dedication, undated; betacam-sp (Box 3, Video-cassette UA10030003-Bcam-0033)
    - Doris Duke Memorial Release Package, 1996 September 10; betacam-sp (Box 3, Video-cassette UA10030003-Bcam-0032)
    - Doris Duke: Doris Duke Bequest News Conference, 1995 March 29; betacam-sp (Box 3, Video-cassette UA10030003-Bcam-0030)
    - Doris Duke: Memorial, Duke Chapel, 1996 September 30; betacam-sp (Box 3, Video-cassette UA10030003-Bcam-0031)
    - Douglas Maitland Knight: Memorial Service, 2005 April 15; betacam-sp (Box 4, Video-cassette UA10030003-Bcam-0054)
    - Freshman Orientation, Tape 2 of 2, 1986 August 28; 3/4-inch (Box 3, Video-cassette UA10030003-Umatic-0039)
      Camera original
    - H. Keith H. Brodie, circa 1993-1999; betacam-sp (Box 2, Video-cassette UA10030003-Bcam-0023)
    - H. Keith H. Brodie, circa 1993-1999; betacam-sp (Box 2, Video-cassette UA10030003-Bcam-0024)
    - H. Keith H. Brodie, circa 1993-1999; betacam-sp (Box 2, Video-cassette UA10030003-Bcam-0025)
    - H. Keith H. Brodie, circa 1993-1999; betacam-sp (Box 2, Video-cassette UA10030003-Bcam-0026)
    - H. Keith H. Brodie, circa 1993-1999; betacam-sp (Box 2, Video-cassette UA10030003-Bcam-0027)
    - H. Keith H. Brodie: Inauguration, 1985 July 1; 3/4-inch (Box 2, Video-cassette UA10030003-Umatic-0029)
    - H. Keith H. Brodie: Inauguration, 1985 July 1; 3/4-inch (Box 2, Video-cassette UA10030003-Umatic-0030)
    - H. Keith H. Brodie: Inauguration, 1985 July 1; 3/4-inch (Box 2, Video-cassette UA10030003-Umatic-0031)
    - H. Keith H. Brodie: Inauguration, 1985 July 1; 3/4-inch (Box 2, Video-cassette UA10030003-Umatic-0032)
    - H. Keith H. Brodie: Inauguration, 1985 July 1; 3/4-inch (Box 2, Video-cassette UA10030003-Umatic-0033)
    - H. Keith H. Brodie: Inauguration, 1985 July 1; 3/4-inch (Box 2, Video-cassette UA10030003-Umatic-0034)
    - H. Keith H. Brodie: Tape 2, circa 1985; 3/4-inch (Box 2, Video-cassette UA10030003-Umatic-0035)
    - Installation of L. Gregory Jones as Dean of the Divinity School, 1997 October 3; betacam-sp (Box 3, Video-cassette UA10030003-Bcam-0040)
    - Jeff and Gregg Foxworthy at Duke Hospital, 1999 January 1; betacam-sp (Box 3, Video-cassette UA10030003-Bcam-0034)
    - Jesse Jackson: Duke Chapel, 1993 March 9; betacam-sp (Box 3, Video-cassette UA10030003-Bcam-0037)
    - Jesse Jackson: Duke Chapel, 1993 March 9; betacam-sp (Box 3, Video-cassette UA10030003-Bcam-0038)
    - Jesse Jackson: Duke Chapel, 1993 March 9; VHS (Box 3, Video-cassette UA10030003-Bcam-0039)
    - John Hope Franklin, undated; betacam-sp (Box 3, Video-cassette UA10030003-Bcam-0036)
    - John Hope Franklin's 80th Birthday, 1995 January 19; betacam-sp (Box 3, Video-cassette UA10030003-Bcam-0035)
    - Library: 4 Millionth Book Ceremony, 1992 April 10; betacam-sp (Box 4, Video-cassette UA10030003-Bcam-0055)
    - Library: 4 Millionth Book Ceremony, 1992 April 10; betacam-sp (Box 4, Video-cassette UA10030003-Bcam-0056)
    - Library: 4 Millionth Book Ceremony, 1992 April 10; betacam-sp (Box 4, Video-cassette UA10030003-Bcam-0057)
    - Nannerl O. Keohane: Founder's Day, 2003; betacam-sp (Box 3, Video-cassette UA10030003-Bcam-0042)
    - Nannerl O. Keohane: Inauguration, 1993 October 23; betacam-sp (Box 4, Video-cassette UA10030003-Bcam-0046)
      camera originals
    - Nannerl O. Keohane: Inauguration, 1993 October 23; betacam-sp (Box 4, Video-cassette UA10030003-Bcam-0047)
    - Nannerl O. Keohane: Inauguration, 1993 October 23; betacam-sp (Box 4, Video-cassette UA10030003-Bcam-0048)
    - Nannerl O. Keohane: Inauguration, 1993 October 23; betacam-sp (Box 4, Video-cassette UA10030003-Bcam-0049)
    - Nannerl O. Keohane: Inauguration, 1993 October 23; betacam-sp (Box 4, Video-cassette UA10030003-Bcam-0050)
    - Nannerl O. Keohane: Inauguration, 1993 October 23; betacam-sp (Box 4, Video-cassette UA10030003-Bcam-0051)
    - Nannerl O. Keohane: Inauguration, 1993 October 23; betacam-sp (Box 4, Video-cassette UA10030003-Bcam-0052)
    - Nannerl O. Keohane: Inauguration, 1993 October 23; betacam-sp (Box 4, Video-cassette UA10030003-Bcam-0053)
    - Nannerl O. Keohane: New President, 1992 December 11; betacam-sp (Box 3, Video-cassette UA10030003-Bcam-0041)
    - Nasher Museum of Art Groundbreaking and Dinner, 2001 December 6; betacam-sp (Box 4, Video-cassette UA10030003-Bcam-0058)
    - Nicholas Family Press Conference, 1995 December 7; betacam-sp (Box 4, Video-cassette UA10030003-Bcam-0059)
    - Nicholas Family Press Conference, 1995 December 7; betacam-sp (Box 4, Video-cassette UA10030003-Bcam-0060)
    - Nicholas School of the Environment Dedication, 1995; betacam-sp (Box 4, Video-cassette UA10030003-Bcam-0061)
    - Nicholas School of the Environment Dedication, 1995; betacam-sp (Box 4, Video-cassette UA10030003-Bcam-0062)
    - Nicholas School of the Environment Dedication, 1995; betacam-sp (Box 4, Video-cassette UA10030003-Bcam-0063)
    - Pearsall, George W.: What is Safe?, Tape 2 of 2, 1985 June 24; 1 videocassette (U-matic) (Box 4, Video-cassette UA10030003-Bcam-0064)
    - Politics of Academic Freedom, Zener Auditorium, 2004 March 1; DVCAM (Box 5, Video-cassette UA10030003-DVCAM-0034)
    - Reynolds Price, 1987 August 16; 3/4-inch (Box 5, Video-cassette UA10030003-Umatic-0042)
      Edit master
    - Richard Brodhead Inauguration: Duke Chapel, 2004 September 18; betacam-sp (Box 1, Video-cassette UA10030003-Bcam-0022)
    - Richard Brodhead Inauguration: Duke Chapel, 2004 September 18; DVCAM (Box 1, Video-cassette UA10030003-DVCAM-0032)
    - Richard Brodhead Inauguration: Faculty Luncheon, Pratt Commons, 2004 September 17; DVCAM (Box 1, Video-cassette UA10030003-DVCAM-0031)
    - Richard Brodhead, Nannerl Keohane, Judy Woodruff: A Conversation in One Brief Afternoon, 2004 February 1; DVD (Box 1, Video-disc UA10030003-OP-0001)
    - Richard Brodhead, Nannerl Keohane, Judy Woodruff: A Conversation in One Brief Afternoon, 2004 February 1; VHS (Box 1, Video-cassette UA10030003-VHS-0029)
    - Richard Brodhead: Inauguration Concert, 2004 September 14; DVCAM (Box 1, Video-cassette UA10030003-DVCAM-0030)
    - Richard Brodhead: Inauguration Concert Program, 2004 September 14 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Richard Brodhead: New President, 2003 December 12; DVCAM (Box 1, Video-cassette UA10030003-DVCAM-0029)
    - Ronald Reagan, undated; 3/4-inch (Box 5, Video-cassette UA10030003-Umatic-0043)
    - Terry Sanford Funeral: #1, 1998 April 22; betacam-sp (Box 5, Video-cassette UA10030003-Bcam-0065)
    - Terry Sanford Funeral: B-Roll, 1998 April 21; betacam-sp (Box 5, Video-cassette UA10030003-Bcam-0064)
    - Terry Sanford Funeral: UNC Feed from SAT Truck, 1998 April 22; VHS (Box 5, Video-cassette UA10030003-VHS-0034)
    - Terry Sanford Funeral: WTVD, 1998 April 22; VHS (Box 5, Video-cassette UA10030003-VHS-0033)
    - Terry Sanford Funeral: WUNC-TV, 1998 April 22; betacam-sp (Box 5, Video-cassette UA10030003-Bcam-0066)
    - Terry Sanford Funeral: WUNC-TV, 1998 April 22; betacam-sp (Box 5, Video-cassette UA10030003-Bcam-0067)
    - Terry Sanford: No. 1, Cameron pre-remarks and show, circa 1985; 3/4-inch (Box 5, Video-cassette UA10030003-Umatic-0045)
    - Terry Sanford: Retirement, 1985; 3/4-inch (Box 5, Video-cassette UA10030003-Umatic-0044)
    - Terry Sanford: Sanford Retirement Gala, no. 3 of 3, 1985; 3/4-inch (Box 5, Video-cassette UA10030003-Umatic-0046)
    - Terry Sanford: tent, march, opening interior, circa 1985; 3/4-inch (Box 5, Video-cassette UA10030003-Umatic-0047)
    - Video New Releases, 1993 November 4, undated; betacam-sp (Box 5, Video-cassette UA10030003-Bcam-0068)
  - Campus Events Related to September 11, 2001, 2001-2002; 1.3
    - 9/11: Perspectives and Policy Implications: Faculty Panel, 2002 September 11; DVCAM (Box 6, Video-cassette UA10030003-DVCAM-0014)
    - Al Jazeera Event, 2002 February 27; DVCAM (Box 6, Video-cassette UA10030003-DVCAM-0013)
    - Christianity, War, and Patriotism, York Chapel, 2001 September 25; DVCAM (Box 6, Video-cassette UA10030003-DVCAM-0006)
    - Interfaith Prayer Vigil, Duke Chapel Quad, 2001 September 12; DVCAM (Box 6, Video-cassette UA10030003-DVCAM-0002)
    - Joseph Lieberman: 2001 Terry Sanford Distinguished Lecturer, 2001 October 28; DVCAM (Box 6, Video-cassette UA10030003-DVCAM-0011)
    - Joseph Lieberman: 2001 Terry Sanford Distinguished Lecturer Program, 2001 October 28 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Medical Aspects of Terrorism, 2001 November 26; DVCAM (Box 6, Video-cassette UA10030003-DVCAM-0012)
    - Memorial Concert, Duke Chapel, 2001 September 30; DVCAM (Box 6, Video-cassette UA10030003-DVCAM-0004)
    - Memorial Concert, Duke Chapel, 2001 September 30; VHS (Box 6, Video-cassette UA10030003-VHS-0002)
    - Memorial Concert, Duke Chapel, Program and Flyer, 2001 September 30 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - President Keohane panel on Fragmentation, 2001 September 16; DVCAM (Box 6, Video-cassette UA10030003-DVCAM-0003)
    - President Keohane panel on Fragmentation, 2001 September 16; VHS (Box 6, Video-cassette UA10030003-VHS-0001)
    - Technology for Counter Terrorism, Pratt School of Engineering, 2001 October 25; DVCAM (Box 6, Video-cassette UA10030003-DVCAM-0010)
    - Terrorism Crisis and the World Economy: What Effects, What Strategies?, Fuqua School of Business, 2001 October 8; DVCAM (Box 6, Video-cassette UA10030003-DVCAM-0008)
    - The Morality of War in Islamic and Christian Perspective, York Chapel, 2001 October 9; DVCAM (Box 6, Video-cassette UA10030003-DVCAM-0009)
    - The New War on Terrorism: Initial Assessments, Sanford Institute, 2001 September 24; DVCAM (Box 6, Video-cassette UA10030003-DVCAM-0005)
    - World Trade Center Disaster Forum, Law School, 2001 October 2; DVCAM (Box 6, Video-cassette UA10030003-DVCAM-0007)
  - Commencement Ceremonies, 1984-2003; 1.4
    - Baccalaureate, 2003; DVCAM (Box 9, Video-cassette UA10030003-DVCAM-0035)
    - Baccalaureate, 2003; DVCAM (Box 9, Video-cassette UA10030003-DVCAM-0036)
    - Baccalaureate, 2002; VHS (Box 9, Video-cassette UA10030003-VHS-0038)
    - Baccalaureate, 2002; VHS (Box 9, Video-cassette UA10030003-VHS-0039)
    - Baccalaureate, 2002; VHS (Box 9, Video-cassette UA10030003-VHS-0040)
    - Commencement, 1984 May; 3/4-inch (Box 7, Video-cassette UA10030003-Umatic-0009)
    - Commencement Camera Original, 1988 May 08; VHS (Box 7, Video-cassette UA10030003-VHS-0003)
    - Commencement Camera Original 1 of 4, 1987; 3/4-inch (Box 7, Video-cassette UA10030003-Umatic-0013)
    - Commencement Camera Original 2 of 4, 1987; 3/4-inch (Box 7, Video-cassette UA10030003-Umatic-0014)
    - Commencement Camera Original 3 of 4, 1987; 3/4-inch (Box 7, Video-cassette UA10030003-Umatic-0015)
    - Commencement Camera Original 4 of 4, 1987; 3/4-inch (Box 7, Video-cassette UA10030003-Umatic-0016)
    - Commencement Exercises Camera Original Tape 1 of 3, 1986 May 4; 3/4-inch (Box 7, Video-cassette UA10030003-Umatic-0010)
    - Commencement Exercises Camera Original Tape 2 of 3, 1986 May 4; 3/4-inch (Box 7, Video-cassette UA10030003-Umatic-0011)
    - Commencement Exercises Camera Original Tape 3 of 3, 1986 May 4; 3/4-inch (Box 7, Video-cassette UA10030003-Umatic-0012)
    - Duke Graduation, 1998 May 17; betacam-sp (Box 9, Video-cassette UA10030003-Bcam-0079)
    - Duke Graduation, 1998 May 17; betacam-sp (Box 9, Video-cassette UA10030003-Bcam-0080)
    - Duke Graduation, 1998 May 17; betacam-sp (Box 9, Video-cassette UA10030003-Bcam-0081)
    - Duke Graduation, 1998 May 17; betacam-sp (Box 9, Video-cassette UA10030003-Bcam-0082)
    - Duke Graduation, 1998 May 17; betacam-sp (Box 9, Video-cassette UA10030003-Bcam-0083)
    - Duke Graduation, 1998 May 17; betacam-sp (Box 9, Video-cassette UA10030003-Bcam-0084)
    - Duke Graduation, 1998 May 17; betacam-sp (Box 9, Video-cassette UA10030003-Bcam-0085)
    - Duke Graduation, 1998 May 17; betacam-sp (Box 9, Video-cassette UA10030003-Bcam-0086)
    - Duke Graduation, 1998 May 17; betacam-sp (Box 9, Video-cassette UA10030003-Bcam-0087)
    - Duke Graduation, 1998 May 17; betacam-sp (Box 9, Video-cassette UA10030003-Bcam-0088)
    - Duke Graduation, 1998 May 17; betacam-sp (Box 9, Video-cassette UA10030003-Bcam-0089)
    - Duke Graduation, 1998 May 17; betacam-sp (Box 9, Video-cassette UA10030003-Bcam-0090)
    - Duke University Baccalaureate Service, 1999 May 14; VHS (Box 9, Video-cassette UA10030003-VHS-0036)
    - Duke University Baccalaureate Service, 1999 May 15; VHS (Box 9, Video-cassette UA10030003-VHS-0037)
    - Duke University Graduation Exercises, 1997 May 18; betacam-sp (Box 9, Video-cassette UA10030003-Bcam-0074)
    - Duke University Graduation Exercises, 1997 May 18; betacam-sp (Box 9, Video-cassette UA10030003-Bcam-0075)
    - Duke University Graduation Exercises, 1997 May 18; betacam-sp (Box 9, Video-cassette UA10030003-Bcam-0076)
    - Duke University Graduation Exercises, 1997 May 18; betacam-sp (Box 9, Video-cassette UA10030003-Bcam-0077)
    - Duke University Graduation Exercises, 1997 May 18; betacam-sp (Box 9, Video-cassette UA10030003-Bcam-0078)
    - Graduation, 1993 May 16; betacam-sp (Box 8, Video-cassette UA10030003-Bcam-0069)
      edit masters: 2 videocassettes (betacam SP) dub of edit master #2: 1 videocassette (betacam SP)
    - Graduation, 1993 May 16; betacam-sp (Box 8, Video-cassette UA10030003-Bcam-0070)
    - Graduation, 1993 May 16; betacam-sp (Box 8, Video-cassette UA10030003-Bcam-0071)
    - Graduation, 1997; betacam-sp (Box 8, Video-cassette UA10030003-Bcam-0072)
    - Graduation, 1997; betacam-sp (Box 8, Video-cassette UA10030003-Bcam-0073)
    - Graduation, 1999 May 16; betacam-sp (Box 9, Video-cassette UA10030003-Bcam-0091)
    - Graduation, 1999 May 16; betacam-sp (Box 9, Video-cassette UA10030003-Bcam-0092)
    - Graduation, 1999 May 16; betacam-sp (Box 9, Video-cassette UA10030003-Bcam-0093)
    - Graduation, 1999 May 16; betacam-sp (Box 9, Video-cassette UA10030003-Bcam-0094)
    - Graduation, 1999 May 16; betacam-sp (Box 9, Video-cassette UA10030003-Bcam-0095)
    - Graduation, 1999 May 16; betacam-sp (Box 9, Video-cassette UA10030003-Bcam-0096)
    - Graduation, 1999 May 16; betacam-sp (Box 9, Video-cassette UA10030003-Bcam-0097)
    - Graduation, 1999 May 16; betacam-sp (Box 9, Video-cassette UA10030003-Bcam-0098)
    - Graduation, 1999 May 16; betacam-sp (Box 9, Video-cassette UA10030003-Bcam-0099)
    - Graduation, 1999 May 16; betacam-sp (Box 9, Video-cassette UA10030003-Bcam-0100)
    - Graduation, 1999 May 16; betacam-sp (Box 9, Video-cassette UA10030003-Bcam-0101)
    - Graduation, 1999 May 16; betacam-sp (Box 9, Video-cassette UA10030003-Bcam-0102)
    - Graduation, 1989; 3/4-inch (Box 8, Video-cassette UA10030003-Umatic-0048)
    - Graduation, 1989; 3/4-inch (Box 8, Video-cassette UA10030003-Umatic-0049)
    - Graduation, 1989; 3/4-inch (Box 8, Video-cassette UA10030003-Umatic-0050)
    - Graduation, 1989; 3/4-inch (Box 8, Video-cassette UA10030003-Umatic-0051)
    - Graduation, 1990; 3/4-inch (Box 8, Video-cassette UA10030003-Umatic-0052)
    - Graduation, 1990; 3/4-inch (Box 8, Video-cassette UA10030003-Umatic-0053)
    - Graduation, 1990; 3/4-inch (Box 8, Video-cassette UA10030003-Umatic-0054)
    - Graduation, 1991 May 12; 3/4-inch (Box 8, Video-cassette UA10030003-Umatic-0055)
    - Graduation, 1991 May 12; 3/4-inch (Box 8, Video-cassette UA10030003-Umatic-0056)
    - Graduation, 1991 May 12; 3/4-inch (Box 8, Video-cassette UA10030003-Umatic-0057)
    - Graduation, 1989; VHS (Box 8, Video-cassette UA10030003-VHS-0035)
      Edit masters